<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Polish City Club on Polish City club</title>
    <link>https://polishcityclub.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Polish City Club on Polish City club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://polishcityclub.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact us if you:
 would like to join our club are a Polish society, club or an organization wishing to work with us on an idea or an initiative you find compelling are a Polish company looking to expand to the UK are a Polish entrepreneur looking to raise funding in London  We look forward to hearing from you!
You can contact us at polishcityclub.org@gmail.com or leave a message using the contact form below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event with Greg Hands MP</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/events/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/events/1/</guid>
      <description>On 6th June we will have a PCC event at the House of Commons with Greg Hands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry Balani on Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/events/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/events/3/</guid>
      <description>On 4th March we will have the pleasure of speaking to Henry Balani about why the Blockchain matters – and why it is different from Bitcoin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honorary Members</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/honorary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/honorary/</guid>
      <description>Count Adam Zamoyski Historian, author of books on Polish history
George Dobry CBE, QC A distinguished English Judge
Mr Grzegorz Król Managing Director, Nestle UK HE
Mr Jan Krzysztof Bielecki Former Prime Minister of Poland, President of Pekao SA, Warsaw, Poland
Mr Jean Lemierre Former President of the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development
Mr Kazimierz Marcinkiewicz Former Prime Minister of Poland; Director for Poland/Albania/Bulgaria, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/join-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/join-us/</guid>
      <description>How to join us? Members who join the Polish City Club meet the following criteria:
 Are over 21 years old. Are of Polish origin or have any connection to, or interest in, Poland Have a university degree or are directors in a UK company Have a few years of experience working as a professional in the UK Agree with the aims and objectives of the Club, as set out in the statute Pay an annual membership fee of £130  If you meet the above criteria and would like to join please fill our contact form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/members/</guid>
      <description>The Members of our Club are highly skilled, experienced and successful professionals who are enthusiastic and motivated to dedicate their time and energy in helping each other as well as acting in the interest of Poland. They share common values and believe in the ethos of mutual respect and open discussions. They act to promote the good name and image of Poland.
The Club membership offers our members a wide range of benefits that include an opportunity to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/membership/</guid>
      <description>You can now pay your membership fee for 2019 through PayPal. Click the link below and follow the steps.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCC Event with Ania Lichota Executive Coach &amp; AGM</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/events/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/events/2/</guid>
      <description>On 20th June we will start with our Annual General Meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCC structure</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/structure/</guid>
      <description>PCC management team:
 Rafal Libera – President Lukasz Rzeczkowski – Board member Martyna Polak – Board member Dawid Szymanek – Board member Roch Glowacki – Board member Pawel Sawicz – Board member  Co-founders:
 Roksana Ciurysek Justyna Jackholt Radek Iling Piotr Michalik Piotr Grzeskiewicz
  Past Presidents:
 2004 – 2005 Piotr Michalik 2005 – 2006 Justyna Jackholt 2006 – 2008 Roksana Ciurysek-Gedir 2008 – 2010 Daniel Stachowiak 2011 – 2015 Dorota Zimnoch 2015 – 2016 Aneta Buchert 2016 – 2019 Jakub Molski  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/press/</guid>
      <description>Articles and videos featuring Polish City Club and its members Puls Biznesu, 11.10.2015 Elita nie chce wracać do kraju
http://m.pb.pl/4318841,41180,elita-nie-chce-wracac-do-kraju?dimension=667
Rzeczpospolita, 6.10.2015 Wolą karierę na Wyspach niż powrót do kraju
http://www4.rp.pl/Sciezki-kariery/310069761-Wola-kariere-na-Wyspach-niz-powrot-do-kraju.html&amp;amp;template=printart
Nature Magazine, 1.10.2015 Nicolas T. Courtois in the article ‘Bitcoin and beyond’
http://www.nature.com/news/the-future-of-cryptocurrencies-bitcoin-and-beyond-1.18447
Dziennik Gazeta Prawna, 12.09.2015 Korpomafia znad Wisły: Prezesami Microsoftu i Google’a wkrótce będą Polacy?
http://biznes.gazetaprawna.pl/artykuly/893394,korpomafia-znad-wisly-prezesami-microsoftu-i-google-a-wkrotce-beda-polacy.html
Tok FM, 27.08.2015 Prezes PCC w audycji ‘Co sie stalo?’</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomasz Czechowicz (MCI)</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/events/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/events/4/</guid>
      <description>On 31st October we will have the pleasure of speaking to Tomasz Czechowicz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we do</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/activities/</guid>
      <description>Guest speaker series In order to broaden network, knowledge and professional aspirations of our members we organise evening gatherings to which we invite interesting, Polish or international speakers from area of politics, academia or business. An hour or so the presentation of our guest is usually followed by a Q&amp;amp;A session, drinks and networking opportunity. Those who expressed their interest before the event may then accompany the guest at a dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who we are</title>
      <link>https://polishcityclub.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polishcityclub.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Polish City Club (PCC) is a members-only organization founded by Polish professionals working in London.
The Club’s mission is to integrate the professionals interested in building a well connected and successful Polish diaspora in the UK, actively promote Poland, facilitate knowledge exchange among Polish professionals, politicians and international communities and increase the interest of international business communities in Poland-related issues.
The objectives of our Club include:
 Integration of community of Polish professionals living in London by building a well-connected and successful Polish diaspora in the UK Acting as a platform of integration and know-how exchange among Club members, politicians, academics and members of international business communities Promoting the image of Poland in the UK Promoting awareness among the business community at large of economic, political and other developments related to Poland Cooperating with the governmental bodies and think-tanks to represent Polish interests in the UK    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>